{
    "id": "4fa514caa9144d8d87ab2aa079414226",
    "title": "Rewrite the sentences correctly",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b5a950fc8eb7405faadac1fb24bd2553",
            "title": "Sentence Correction Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "My father knows how to teach English .............................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "well",
                        "good"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We want a new house to ....................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "live",
                        "live in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ....................................... for you since 9 oâ€™clock in the morning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am waiting",
                        "have been waiting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "James ..................................... suffering from fever since yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "was",
                        "has been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Neither Ann nor Mary .................................... arrived.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will call on you before I .....................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "leave",
                        "will leave"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ..................................... all the books to the library yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "returned",
                        "have returned"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Each man and each woman ...................................... the right to vote.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Walking along the road, the old man was .............................. by a bus.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ran over",
                        "run over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ...................................... hard for the last two weeks.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is studying",
                        "was studying",
                        "has been studying"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am not used ...................................... in busy streets.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to drive",
                        "driving",
                        "to driving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The poet and dramatist ....................................... dead.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}